{
"question": "六",
"answer": "ろく"
},
{
"question": "四つ",
"answer": "よっつ"
},
{
"question": "丈夫",
"answer": "じょうぶ"
},
{
"question": "毎晩",
"answer": "まいばん"
},
{
"question": "東-1",
"answer": "ひがし"
},
{
"question": "五つ",
"answer": "いつつ"
},
{
"question": "晴れ",
"answer": "はれ"
},
{
"question": "細い",
"answer": "ほそい"
},
{
"question": "廊下",
"answer": "ろうか"
},
{
"question": "太い",
"answer": "ふとい"
},
{
"question": "縦",
"answer": "たて"
},
{
"question": "七つ",
"answer": "ななつ"
},
{
"question": "九つ",
"answer": "ここのつ"
},
{
"question": "留学生",
"answer": "りゅうがくせい"
},
{
"question": "一昨年",
"answer": "おととし"
},
{
"question": "人",
"answer": "ひと"
},
{
"question": "居る",
"answer": "いる"
},
{
"question": "其れ",
"answer": "それ"
},
{
"question": "物",
"answer": "もの"
},
{
"question": "家",
"answer": "いえ"
},
